Let's see how you can optimize your bid with Sponsored display.
When you're setting up your campaign, you'll see three choices in the bidding section.
Optimize for reach, which helps your ad show to as many customers as possible.
Optimize for page visits to drive consideration by showing your ad to shoppers more likely to click.
And optimize for conversions to help drive purchases by showing your ad to shoppers more likely
to purchase.
If we find an opportunity where your ad is more likely to achieve the goal you optimize for,
we might increase your bid by up to 300 percent.
If it's less likely, we might lower it.
Choose the right bid optimization strategy for your goal and continue with the rest of your campaign.